http://anyvite.com/privacypolicy

Privacy Policy
It is Simpletastic Inc. ("Simpletastic")'s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Simpletastic collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Simpletastic's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Simpletastic's visitors use its website. From time to time, Simpletastic may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Simpletastic also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Simpletastic does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Simpletastic's websites choose to interact with Simpletastic in ways that require Simpletastic to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Simpletastic gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register and login at Simpletastic to provide a valid email address. Those who engage in transactions with Simpletastic - by registering, for example - are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Simpletastic collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Simpletastic. Simpletastic does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Simpletastic may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Simpletastic may monitor the most popular parts of the Simpletastic site, and log page views. Simpletastic may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Simpletastic does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Simpletastic discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Simpletastic's behalf or to provide services available at Simpletastic's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Simpletastic's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Simpletastic will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Simpletastic discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Simpletastic believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Simpletastic, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Simpletastic website and have supplied your email address, Simpletastic may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Simpletastic and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Simpletastic takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Simpletastic uses cookies to help Simpletastic identify and track visitors, their usage of Simpletastic website, and their website access preferences. Simpletastic visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Simpletastic's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Simpletastic's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Simpletastic may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Simpletastic's sole discretion. Simpletastic encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
© Simpletastic Inc.
